bestwebbuys.com 2014-04-22

# Best Web Buys searches online stores to find the lowest prices for books, music, and more.

est Web Buys has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the following websites: 

> 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, and to help us make our site more useful to visitors. 

For example, say you arrived to our website by following a link on a website like AboutAerobics.com that talks about [aerobic exercise](http://www.aboutaerobics.com/ "aerobic exercise"). All we will ever know about you is your IP address and that you visited our books section that compares prices of aerobic books. 

**_Sharing of information_**

Best Web Buys does not share any contact information or IP address information with its partners. In the future, Best Web Buys may use select customer information such as your zip code to help us calculate more precise shipping costs and sales tax. However, Best Web Buys does not share any personally identifiable customer information with our partners. We will only use information that helps our customers to find the lowest prices. 

Best Web Buys links to its partner sites. Best Web Buys is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

In addition, Best Web Buys technology powers select partner web sites. Best Web Buys search technology in used on partner web sites to power their product comparison services. In these cases, Best Web Buys does not share any user information with our licensees. 

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

We run contests and scholarship programs on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their mailing and email addresses). The customer's contact information is used to contact them when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Some ads served on our site may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

**_Children's Privacy_**

Pursuant to the [Children's Online Privacy Protection Act](http://www.ftc.gov/os/1999/9910/64fr59888.htm), which became effective on April 21, 2000, we cannot collect personal information from children under 13 years of age without the consent of their parents. _Personal information_ includes any information which can uniquely identify a child and includes information such as name and e-mail address. 

Since we do not have the resources to verify parental consent, we have decided not to accept **any** personal information from children under 13 years of age. This means that we will not accept contest entries, surveys, or user registration from children under 13 years of age. 

**_Security_**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

**_Supplementary Information_**

This site supplements the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties. 

**_Choice/Opt-Out_**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

To have your name removed from our database, to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service, send email to [webmaster@bestwebbuys.com](mailto:webmaster@bestwebbuys.com) . 

**_Correct/Update_**

To change or modify personal profile information previously provided, send email to [webmaster@bestwebbuys.com](mailto:webmaster@bestwebbuys.com) . 

**_Contacting Best Web Buys_**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: 

> Best Web Buys  
>  1150 Foothill Blvd, Suite J  
>  La Canada, CA 91011  
> 

|
